&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：有一种相信的诱惑，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is a temptation to believe, and
这是社区中的一种邪教感觉，
it's sort of a cult feeling among the community,
大多数开发人员倾向于认为隐式机制是神奇的。
most developers tend to think that implicit mechanisms are magical.
当一些事情发生在幕后，而它并不明显，
That when something happens underneath the scenes, and it wasn't obvious,
那就是某种魔法
then it's some sort of magic.
我们倾向于把魔法等同于邪恶，
And we tend to equate magic with bad, evil,
这样不好，因为我不能理解发生了什么。
like this is not good because I can't understand what's happening.
这就是为什么反强制的前景
And this is a predominant reason why that anti-coercion prospective
存在是因为人们觉得强迫的隐蔽性是没落的
exists is because people feel like the implicitness of coercion is the downfall
其中他们指出了Java或C+之类的类型转换的显性。
where they point to explicitness of type casting in something like Java or C++.
然后他们说
And then they say,
您永远不会自动将整数转换为浮点数或其他任何形式。
you would never automatically convert an integer into a float or whatever.
但是JavaScript做了所有这种自动的事情，然后他们说，好吧，
But JavaScript does all this sort of automatic stuff and then they say, well,
这是JavaScript的一个弱点，因为它既神奇又糟糕。
that's a weakness of JavaScript because it's magical and bad.
我不认为是这两件事中的任何一件，
I don't think it's either of those things,
我认为我们应该把含蓄看作抽象。
I think that we should think about implicitness as abstraction.
并不是所有的抽象都是好的，但是一些抽象是必要的。
Not all abstractions are good, but some abstractions are necessary.
隐含，我们这里不是在处理函数式编程。
Implicitness, and we're not dealing with functional programming here.
这不是这个课程，那是不同的课程。
This is not this course, that's a different course.
这里有一个插头，你可以查看我的函数式编程课程。
Here's a plug, you can check on my functional programming course.
但在函数式编程中，您可以到处使用抽象。
But within functional programming, you use abstraction all over the place.
事实证明，声明性编码风格实际上更隐含。
And it turns out that the declarative style of coding is actually more implicit.
所以含蓄并不是坏事，它是阻碍的恰当用法。
So implicitness is not bad, it is the proper usage of obstruction.
换句话说，我们想隐藏关键的不必要的细节，为什么？
In other words, we want to hide key unnecessary details, why?
因为这会让读者重新关注重要的东西。
Because that re-focuses the reader on the important stuff.
我们不是用他们不需要的东西来分散他们的注意力。
We're not distracting them with the stuff that they don't need.
我们想聚焦他们。
We wanna focus them.
我们想通过重新聚焦来增加代码的清晰度。
We wanna increase the clarity of the code by re-focusing.
所以JavaScript类型系统的一些隐含本质是粗略的，
So some of the implicit nature of JavaScript's type system is sketchy,
但其中一些是相当有用的。
but some of it is quite useful.
比如拳击。
For example, the boxing.
这是隐含的，但也非常有用，因为不得不
That's implicit, but also very useful, because the distraction of having to
在大多数情况下，我会争辩说，把它扔进一个物体并不是，
cast it into an object isn't, what I would argue in most cases,
读者不需要的不必要的细节。
an unnecessary detail that the reader doesn't need.
这实际上是JavaScript的DNA。
And that's actually at the DNA of JavaScript.
JavaScript具有如此低的进入壁垒的部分原因
Part of the reason JavaScript has such a low barrier to entry
是因为它不会强迫读者处理一堆不必要的细节。
is because it doesn't force the reader to deal with a bunch of unnecessary detail.
它背叛了JavaScript的DNA来暗示所有这些隐含的
It betrays JavaScript's DNA to suggest that all those implicit
有些事情是我们应该避免的。
things are things that we should avoid.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以在这里，如果我写字符串是为了让它非常明显，我是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So here, if I'm writing string to make it super obvious that I'm
把这东西弄成一根绳子，我不知道，我觉得这会让人分心。
gonna make this thing into a string, I don't know, I think that's distracting.
我想我会把号码放进去
I think I would just drop in the number and
非常高兴，因为我知道这个数字永远不会出现在任何一个角落里
be perfectly happy, because I know that number is never in any of those corner
有些事情可能会很奇怪。
cases where something could be weird.
例如，也许我已经检查过，以确保num Students不是NaN。
Maybe I've already checked to make sure that num students is not nan, for example.
所有其他的数字，它可能不是负零和
All the other numbers that it could possibly be other than negative zero and
南，这些是我唯一需要担心的角落案件。
nan, those are my only corner cases that I need to worry about here.
因此，如果我有处理这些角落情况的if语句，那么这行
So if I have if statements that deal with those corner cases, then this line of
代码，第4行，实际上是更好的沟通，因为它适当地让
code, line 4, is actually better communication, cuz it properly lets
JavaScript抽象了当时不需要处理的细节。
JavaScript abstract the detail that's not necessary to deal with at that moment.
这是另一个例子，小于运算符，
Here's another example, the less than operator,
我们讨论了它是如何将事物强制成数字的。
we talked about how it coerces things into numbers.
有时你想继续前进
Sometimes you wanna go ahead and
确保它们都是一个数字，这样你就不会得到一些奇怪的东西。
make sure that both of them are a number so that you don't get something weird.
例如，如果它们都是字符串，则不会将它们都转换为数字。
For example, if both of them are strings, it doesn't turn them both into numbers.
小于运算符进行字母数字比较。
The less than operator does an alphanumeric comparison.
所以有一个角落的情况，如果你可能有一个小于适用于两个
So there's a corner case, if you could possibly have a less than applied to two
字符串，您可能希望首先确定它们都是数字。
strings, you probably do wanna make sure that they're both numbers first.
但如果我在代码的某个地方，我知道其中至少有一个是
But if I'm in a place of the code where I know at least one of them is
肯定是个数字？
definitely a number?
好吧，那么，我知道另一个会变成一个数字，所以可能不是
Well then, I know the other one's gonna become a number, so maybe it's not
为了迫使你读到我让他们两个都是数字的事实。
necessary to force you to read the fact that I'm making them both numbers.
也许它是好的，让小于操作符做强制形式。
Maybe it's okay, to let that less than operator do the coercion form.
这些不是硬性规定，
These are not hard and fast rules,
这些都是试图训练你这样思考和分析。
these are trying to train you to think like this to analyze.
如果你在一个地方，你可以选择使用强制手段，但是
And if you are in a place where you have the choice to use coercion but
这并不明显，这是在你的职权范围内，使它显而易见。
it's not obvious, it's within your purview to make it obvious.
很明显他们都是数字和
Make it obvious that they're both numbers and
因此，我不需要担心显式转换它们。
therefore, I don't need to worry about explicitly casting them.
很明显它们都是数字。
It's just already obvious that they're both numbers.
如果您传达了这个意图，它就不会绊倒代码的其他读取器。
If you communicate that intent, it's not gonna trip up other readers of the code.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：真的，问题是，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Really, the question is,
显示这些额外的细节对读者有没有帮助？
is showing these extra details helpful to the reader or not?
有时是，有时不是。
Sometimes yes, sometimes no.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：基本上，我要求你们成为批判性的，分析性的思想家，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Basically, I'm asking you to be critical, analytical thinkers,
做一名工程师而不是代码猴子，好吗？
to be an engineer and not a code monkey, okay?